{"data":[{"question":"We had dinner _____ an Italian restaurant last night","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"There was another protest ____ campus yesterday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\non\/off campus\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Our company has stores _____ 12 states.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Norton gave his presentation _____ the meeting yesterday","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Senator Johnson spoke _____ the memorial service last Friday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"What have you got _____ your bag.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"There are a few shops _____ the end of the street.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"The picture is _____ the wall.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Milan is _____ the north of Italy.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In the north\/south...of somewhere","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"There's somebody waiting _____ the bus stop.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"}]}